const STORE = {
  
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Portobello and Shiitake are types of what food item?',
      options: [
        'Red Wine',
        'Apples',
        'Mushrooms',
        'Potatoes',
      ],
      answer: 'Mushrooms'
    },
    {
      question:
        'The side dish couscous is made primarily from what?',
        options:[
          'Garbanzo beans',
          'Meat',
          'Rice',
          'Wheat',
        ],
        answer:
          'Wheat'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Caesar salad was first prepared in what country?',
        options:[
          'Mexico',
          'Russia',
          'Italy',
          'Canada',
        ],
        answer:
          'Mexico'
    },
       {
       question:
         'Plantain is similar to which common fruit?',
         options:[
           'Bananas',
           'Pomegranate',
           'Avocado',
           'Jackfruit',
         ],
         answer:
           'Bananas'
     },
     {
       question:
         'In Japanese cooking, what is Nori?',
         options:[
           'Seaweed',
           'Noodles',
           'Egg',
           'Tofu',
         ],
         answer:
           'Seaweed'
     },
     {
       question:
         'What food is hummus made from?',
         options:[
           'Mung beans',
           'Chickpeas',
           'Cauliflower',
           'Eggplant',
         ],
         answer:
           'Chickpeas'
     },
     {
       question:
         'Sauerkraut is made of which vegetable?',
         options:[
           'Cauliflower',
           'Lettuce',
           'Cabbage',
           'Spinach',
         ],
         answer:
           'Cabbage'
     },
     {
       question:
         'The rice dish Paella comes from what country?',
         options:[
           'Italy',
           'Spain',
           'Greece',
           'America',
         ],
         answer: 'Spain'
     },
     {
       question:
         'What food is used as the base of Guacamole?',
         options:[
           'Onions',
           'Cilantro',
           'Avocado',
           'Tomatoes',
         ],
         answer: 'Avocado'
     },
     {
       question:
         'Deer meat is known by what name?',
         options:[
           'Jamon',
           'Venison',
           'Prosciutto',
           'Mutton',
         ],
         answer: 'Venison'
     }
  ],

  currentQuestion: 0,
  score : 0,

}


